ecchira ochira sa   kamome no nakigoe kikitsutsu
Chugging and chuffing along the ocean listening to cries of seagulls
donbura donbura to   nami ni yurare yuku shima wa
Rolling and roiling waves rocking the boat I’m sailing to the isle
okaruto airando
Island of the occult
takanaru kokoro mo osaezu...
My mind is racing and my heart is thumping...
yorokobi ga unaru! chishikiyoku kamishimete!
Surging ecstasy! Savoring the taste of curiosity!
nandomo nandomo sa   noroi no shomotsu yomiasatte mo
Time after time after time   I studied the contents of the cursed grimoires
dou ni mo kou ni mo ne   wakannee koto bakari aru
Mulled over page after page   The whole thing nothing but gobbledegook
...ga! Goodbye nayami!
...But! Goodbye, worrying!
sayounara hikikomori no hibi
And adios to my days of inside living
nengan no nazo no kotou ni tadoritsuita!
I am here at last, standing on the shore of an isle of mystery!
kaidoku dekita watashi nomi wo yurusu hiroma wa
Only one who cracks the code can enter this spacious room and
nantomo mabayui...
Gosh, how bright it shines...
doko kashiko mo ougon! ougon!
There and everywhere is gold and more gold!
Yahoo! Pa Pa Ya! Ah...
kindan no etsuraku de aru to shirinagara
Knowing all along that this is the fruit of a forbidden paradise
(null sieben fünfzehn elf neunundzwanzig)
(zero seven fifteen eleven twenty-nine)
dongara byunbyun to   iya na oto ga kikoete kuru
Clash clatter zip swish thunk   Dreadful noises are coming from somewhere
masaka masaka na   dare mo inai hazu na no ni
Must be mistaken, I think   There shouldn’t be anybody here but me
kono shima nan nan sa...
What is this island’s deal...?
wakideru fuan o yosome ni
Pretending not to notice worry rising,
ashidori wa oku e oku e to hikikomarete...
I followed the noise and let myself be drawn in deeper, deeper still...
konjiki chouchou ni
Golden butterfly breed
matowaritsuku nanatsu no kui
Septuple stakes that clatter round at high speed
bureedo ni bariyaa ni
Blades and barriers lead
akai moji yara aoi moji...
To red text and even blue to read
konrinzai yameta! sayounara okaruto no shima yo
Yep, screw this, I am out! Goodbye forever, you occultic island
mou nido to tachiiru koto wa shimasen kara...
You can bet your life I will never dare to set foot here again...
tojikomerarete chibiru watashi
But fear strikes, I’m trapped in here
sakebu kotoba ga...
And the words I shout out are,
koko wa doko?!
“Where on Earth am I?!”
majo darake no hentai kuukan?!
“A perverted region packed with witches?!”
Oh No! My God... Ha...!!
densetsu wa usan no mi to tomo ni kakusarete
Then the legend’s lost, hidden alongside a very fishy fruit
(null sieben fünfzehn elf neunundzwanzig)
(zero seven fifteen eleven twenty-nine)